

Leandro Tagaro

Graphic Designer

CONTACT

- 0154, Manga National H.S Road Uptown, Ubujan Dist., Tagb. City
- drewtags32@gmail.com
- 09451647989

FOLLOW ME

- www.facebook.com/drotagars
- www.instagram.com/dro_otso2x

REFERENCE

- Optometrist, Proprietor of EyeChoice Optical Clinic, DYRD Bldg., Ingles St., Tagb. City 09484641978
- SFO3 Ma. Vilma Lopena
 C, Finance / C, Logistics, Tagbilaran City
 Fire Station
 © 09307038769

SKILLS











Photoshop

Illustrator

tor

Filmora

HTML 5

CSS 3







Microsoft Office

PROFILE

I went to the Holy Name University & Majored in Informtion Management (Computer Science dept.) I gathered a lot of experiences and skills as I had been worked with & I do multitasking and understanding client's artistic preference.

WORK EXPERIENCE

LAYOUT ARTIST (DU EK SAM, Inc)

2019-PRESENT

Design tarpaulin, leaflet, t-shirt, mugs, wall mural, facemask facebook adds, certificates, calling card & website banners.

DATA ENTRY & IT STAFF (Ideal Vision Center)

2011 - 2019

2006 - 2010

2002 - 2006

Input sales and customers data into the system and making monthly and annual reports. Troubleshooting a computer & making a layout design seldomly.

EDUCATION

HOLY NAME UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science in Information Management (ComSci dept.)

HOLY SPIRIT SCHOOL
 High School

HOLY SPIRIT SCHOOL

1998 - 2002 Elementary

Creating designs aesthetically pleasing!